Jhal
ki Welcome to Six, today in this video I will
show you how you can pay the premium of Aditya Birla Sun Life
Insurance online,
it is a very simple
process, you can make the premium payment online, if
you want
you can make the payment from Aditya Birla Capital's website,
otherwise you
can also make the premium payment through Amazon and Paytm, for this you
need the policy number and the
date of birth of the policy holder, so now I will
show you by making the payment, it is such an easy
step, come, you can do it at home, to make the
premium payment, first of all
you have to search on Google Birla Sun
Life Insurance, after this see, there is
an option of Pay Premium, so
click on the premium option here,
after clicking a page will open,
or this page which is opening, here first of all you have to give the
first character
and the
date of birth of today, after that
click on submit, after clicking on submit the
policy amount will be shown, after that you will have to
go to next again, so now I will show you how to do it, now
let me show you, now  Yes, and
you can make payment. There are many options like
net banking, credit card, debit card, you
can make payment through that. So, I have
given everything here. And look here, a
new page has opened. Here the
name of the policy holder is shown, the date is
shown, along with that the
insurance premium is also shown here.
Here it is asking to give email ID and mobile
number because the
receipt will go to the email ID. If you want, you
can also download the receipt. So,
I have given everything here. Now the email ID and
mobile number are left to be given. So,
I have given it here and
clicked next. Look here, the payment
gateway has come there. Here there are
many options like credit card, debit card, net banking, RPSC PTI, so
from here I have made the payment. Here
you can see the transaction ID is
showing, the time is showing and the method by which
I have made the payment is showing here
and the amount I have paid is
showing here. So, it is very easy. You can
easily pay the premium by following this process.
Now you can easily download the receipt from here while sitting at home.
If you need any more
information then you can tell us in the comment.
Thank you for watching the video. To
watch more such videos, please
subscribe to our channel Infosys.